

# Aman Avinash

Student



# **Professional Summary**

Goal oriented student committed to learning, developing skills in Computer Science and Business. Self-directed and energetic with superior performance in both autonomous or collaborative environments. Several years of experience studying computer science through school and other college courses.



# **Professional Experience**

2023-08 -Current

## Coding Tutor

Code Ninjas, Tracy

- Issued reports updating students, parents and teachers on student progress.
- Worked closely with students on specific class struggles, closely reviewing materials and assignments to offer targeted help.
- Assessed student learning needs and provided relevant instruction to close knowledge gaps.
- Used variety of teaching methods to successfully help wide range of students.
- Monitored student progress and provided feedback and support.

2023-08 -Current

#### Soccer Referee

US Soccer Association, San Francisco

- Examined equipment for proper functionality and promoted safe playing conditions.
- Addressed rule infractions or complaints by participants to assess any necessary penalties.
- Officiated at sporting events, games, or competitions to maintain standards of play and



#### **Address**

Mountain House, CA, 95391

#### Phone

1-408-329-8242

#### E-mail

amanavinash007@gmail.co m



Self-Motivated



Excellent

Decision-Making



Excellent

Planning and Coordination



Excellent

Flexible and Adaptable



Excellent

Problem-Solving







Java



Python



Excellent

HTML



JavaScript

verify observed game rules.

- Conferred with other sporting officials, coaches, players and facility managers to provide information, coordinate activities, and discuss problems.
- Enforced discipline to encourage respect, fairness and equality for players.

## 2021-09 -Current

#### **Assistant Event Coordinator**

MOHAM, Mountain House

- Coordinated schedules and timelines for events.
- Performed event coordination for larger parties and gatherings.
- Designed and implemented efforts to publicize events and promote sponsorships.
- Brainstormed and implemented creative event concepts and themes.
- Coordinate community events with over 700 attendees

## 2021-05 -2022-04

#### **Assistant Project Administrator**

Sikhs For Humanity, Tracy

- Delegated assignments based on plans, project needs, and knowledge of individual team members.
- Interacted with customers by phone, email, or in-person to provide information.
- Greeted incoming visitors and customers professionally and provided friendly, knowledgeable assistance.
- Maintained and updated office records, both digital and physical.
- Assisted over 200 people per day

### 2020-11 -2021-04

#### **Tutor**

Smartling Learning Center, Mountain House

- Provided homework assistance using specific curriculum and materials.
- Collaborated with students to complete homework assignments, identify lagging skills, and correct weaknesses.



- Supported students with helpful study habits and exam strategies.
- Collaborated with parents to develop appropriate tutoring lessons.
- Taught students remotely using online video chat platform and other delivery channels.
- Coached and mentored less-experienced tutors to observe and measure outcomes.
- Used personalized learning plans to guide students to deeper understanding of course material and learning styles.



## **Education**

2020-08 -Current

## **High School Diploma**

Mountain House High School - Mountain House, CA

- Completed AP course in Computer Science Principles
- Completed AP course in Computer Science A
- 4.4 GPA



# **Accomplishments**

- Attended International level competition for DECA for Project Management Business Solutions event
  - Placed top 3 at State level competition in DECA
  - Participated for 3 years through regional, state, and international competitions in DECA
  - Active member of the National Technical Honor Society



## **Certifications**

2023-08

Licensed USSF Referee - August 2023 - Dec 2024

2023-10

Cybersecurity Work Experience - Goldman Sachs